Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Freshman (Frosh) Football Film Reels, 1922-2001; 671 items
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn, 11/3/84 - OFF. #1, 1984; 1 item (Item 57)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 9/9/88, 1988; 1 item (Item 58)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 9/9/88 - PASS SKEL (OFF), 1988; 1 item (Item 59)
  - Princeton Scrim - Pass Skeleton, 9/9/86, 1986; 1 item (Item 60)
  - Princeton Scrim - Team Scrum #2 of 2, 9/9/86, 1986; 1 item (Item 61)
  - Princeton/W.M. and Mary, 9/23/89 - #4, 1989; 1 item (Item 62)
  - Princeton/W.M. and Mary, 9/23/89 - #3, 1989; 1 item (Item 63)
  - Princeton/Penn, 10/31/87 - Reels #4, 1987; 1 item (Item 64)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/29/60 - Reel #2, 1960; 1 item (Item 65)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn, 10/29/77 - 1st Half Offense, 1977; 1 item (Item 66)
  - Williams (36)/Bow (6), 10/17/64 - Reel #3, 1964; 1 item (Item 67)
  - Princeton Freshman vs. Penn., 10/29/77 - 2nd Half Offense, 1977; 1 item (Item 68)
  - Princeton Freshman vs. Penn., 10/29/77 - 1st Half Defense, 1977; 1 item (Item 69)
  - Princeton Freshman vs. Penn., 10/29/77 - 2nd Half Defense, 1977; 1 item (Item 70)
  - Princeton DEF. 1 - Wilkes Scrimmage, 9/9/77, 1977; 1 item (Item 71)
  - Princeton OFF. 2 - Wilkes Scrimmage, 9/9/77, 1977; 1 item (Item 72)
  - Williams (36)/Bow (6), 10/17/64 - Reel #1, 1964; 1 item (Item 73)
  - Williams (36)/Bow (6), 10/17/64 - Reel #2, 1964; 1 item (Item 74)
  - Princeton/Brown Print, 10/3/81 - Kicks, 1981; 1 item (Item 75)
  - Princeton/Brown Orig., 10/3/81 - OFF. 1, 1981; 1 item (Item 76)
  - Princeton/Brown Orig., 10/3/81 - OFF. 2, 1981; 1 item (Item 77)
  - Princeton/Brown Print, 10/3/81 - DEF. 1, 1981; 1 item (Item 78)
  - Princeton/Brown Print, 10/3/81 - DEF. 2, 1981; 1 item (Item 79)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth Orig., 9/9/88 - DEF. 2, 1988; 1 item (Item 80)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth Orig., 9/9/88 - PASS SKEL (DEF), 1988; 1 item (Item 81)
  - Princeton/Pennsylvania Freshmen, Reel #3, 1952; 1 item (Item 82)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard Fr., 11/10/56 - Reel #2, 1956; 1 item (Item 83)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Yale Fr., 11/17/56 - Reel #2, 1956; 1 item (Item 84)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Yale Fr., 11/17/56 - Reel #3, 1956; 1 item (Item 85)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/3/56 - Reel #3, 1956; 1 item (Item 86)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Harvard Fr., 11/10/56 - Reel #1, 1956; 1 item (Item 87)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/3/56 - Reel #2, 1956; 1 item (Item 88)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/3/56 - Reel #1, 1956; 1 item (Item 89)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Columbia Fr., 10/27/56 - Reel #3, 1956; 1 item (Item 90)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Columbia Fr., 10/27/56 - Reel #2, 1956; 1 item (Item 91)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Columbia Fr., 10/27/56 - Reel #1, 1956; 1 item (Item 92)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/13/56 - Reel #3, 1956; 1 item (Item 93)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/13/56 - Reel #2, 1956; 1 item (Item 94)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/13/56 - Reel #1, 1956; 1 item (Item 95)
  - Princeton/Pennsylvania Freshmen, Reel #2, 1952; 1 item (Item 96)
  - Princeton/Pennsylvania Freshmen, Reel #1, 1952; 1 item (Item 97)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/1/58 - Reel #2, 1958; 1 item (Item 98)
  - Princeton Fr./Dartmouth, DEF. #2, 1981; 1 item (Item 99)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/8/79 - OFF. #1, 1979; 1 item (Item 100)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/8/79 - OFF. #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 101)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 10/28/72 - Reel #3, 1972; 1 item (Item 102)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 10/28/72 - Reel #2, 1972; 1 item (Item 103)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 10/28/72 - Reel #1, 1972; 1 item (Item 104)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 10/22/71 - 4th Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 105)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 11/4/78 - OFF. #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 106)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 11/4/78 - OFF. #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 107)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 11/4/78 - DEF. #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 108)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 11/4/78 - DEF. #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 109)
  - Princeton B./Montclair, 10/1/79 - DEF., 1979; 1 item (Item 110)
  - Princeton B./Rutgers, 11/79 - Reel #1 OFF., 1979; 1 item (Item 111)
  - Princeton/E. Stroud, 10/19/79 - DEF. #2, 1 item (Item 112)
  - Princeton/Cornell, 10/19/79 - OFF. #1, 1 item (Item 113)
  - Princeton/E. Stroud, 10/19/79 - Kicks, 1 item (Item 114)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn Fr., 10/30/82 - Kicks, 1982; 1 item (Item 115)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Cornell Fr., 10/15/66 - Reel #2, 1966; 1 item (Item 116)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Cornell Fr., 10/15/66 - Reel #3, 1966; 1 item (Item 117)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/28/67 - Reel #2, 1967; 1 item (Item 118)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Cornell Fr., 10/15/66 - Reel #1, 1966; 1 item (Item 119)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/28/67 - Reel #3, 1967; 1 item (Item 120)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn Fr., 10/28/67 - Reel #1, 1967; 1 item (Item 121)
  - Wilkes vs. Princeton, 9/14/74 - Game #2, OFF. #2, 1974; 1 item (Item 122)
  - Wilkes vs. Princeton, 9/14/74 - Game #2, DEF. #2, 1974; 1 item (Item 123)
  - Princeton vs. Wilkes, 9/14/74 - Game #2, OFF. #1, 1974; 1 item (Item 124)
  - Wilkes vs. Princeton, 9/14/74 - Game #2, DEF. #1, 1974; 1 item (Item 125)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/18/70 - 2nd Half DEF., 1970; 1 item (Item 126)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/18/70 - 2nd Half OFF., 1970; 1 item (Item 127)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/18/70 - 1st Half DEF., 1970; 1 item (Item 128)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/18/70 - 1st Half OFF., 1970; 1 item (Item 129)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/11/71 - 2nd Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 130)
  - Navy vs. Princeton University Fresh., 10/19/73 - Reel #2 OFF., 1 item (Item 131)
  - Princeton Football Practice, LB vs. OFF. Line Outside Drill, 8/31/77 - Reel #2, 1977; 1 item (Item 132)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers, 9/27/69 - OFF. 2nd Half, 1969; 1 item (Item 133)
  - Navy vs. Princeton University Fresh., 10/19/73 - Reel #2 DEF., 1 item (Item 134)
  - Penn. vs. Princeton University, 10/26/73 - Reel #3 OFF., 1973; 1 item (Item 135)
  - Penn. vs. Princeton University, 10/26/73 - Reel #1 OFF., 1973; 1 item (Item 136)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/11/71 - 1st Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 137)
  - FROSH - Princeton vs. Harvard, 11/11/73 - OFF., 1973; 1 item (Item 138)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Rutgers, 10/16/71 - Reel #2, 1971; 1 item (Item 139)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers (Freshmen), 10/13/73 - Reel #1, 1973; 1 item (Item 140)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers (Freshmen), 10/13/73 - Reel #2, 1973; 1 item (Item 141)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers (Freshmen), 10/13/73 - Reel #3, 1973; 1 item (Item 142)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers (Freshmen), 10/13/73 - Reel #4, 1973; 1 item (Item 143)
  - Columbia Fr. vs. Princeton University, 11/2/66 - Reel #3, 1966; 1 item (Item 144)
  - Columbia Fr. vs. Princeton University, 11/2/66 - Reel #4, 1966; 1 item (Item 145)
  - Princeton vs. Penn., 10/23/65 - 2nd Quarter, 1965; 1 item (Item 146)
  - Princeton vs. Penn., 10/23/65 - 3rd Quarter, 1965; 1 item (Item 147)
  - Fr. Princeton (27)/Fr. Penn. (20) - 10/22/66, 1966; 1 item (Item 148)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/25/69 - Reel #2, 1969; 1 item (Item 149)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/25/69 - Reel #3, 1969; 1 item (Item 150)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/25/69 - Reel #4, 1969; 1 item (Item 151)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/8/66 - Reel #2, 1966; 1 item (Item 152)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/8/66 - Reel #3, 1966; 1 item (Item 153)
  - Columbia - Princeton Freshman, 1966 - Reel #2, 1 item (Item 154)
  - Columbia - Princeton Freshman, 1966 - Reel #3, 1 item (Item 155)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Rutgers Fr., 10/8/66 - Reel #1, 1966; 1 item (Item 156)
  - Princeton/Penn. Freshmen, 10/26/68, 1968; 1 item (Item 157)
  - Columbia - Princeton Freshman, 1966 - Reel #1, 1 item (Item 158)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/29/60 - Reel #1, 1960; 1 item (Item 159)
  - Princeton vs. Penn., 10/23/65 - 1st Quarter, 1965; 1 item (Item 160)
  - Princeton Football Practice, 5 vs. 5 (Inside Game), 8/31/77 - Reel #3, 1977; 1 item (Item 161)
  - PASS SKELETON DEF., 9/31/77, 1977; 1 item (Item 162)
  - Princeton vs. Rutgers, 9/27/69 - OFF. 2nd Half, 1969; 1 item (Item 163)
  - Princeton Frosh/ Harvard, 10/25/80, 1980; 1 item (Item 164)
  - Princeton Frosh/Columbia, 10/10/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 165)
  - Princeton Frosh/Columbia, 10/10/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 166)
  - Princeton Frosh/Yale, 11/15/80 - DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 167)
  - Princeton U./Penn., 11/1/80 - \"Varsity\" DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 168)
  - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/80 - DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 169)
  - Princeton/Cornell (FROSH), 10/19/84 - DEF. #1, 1 item (Item 170)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/15/86 - Reel #5 DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 171)
  - Princeton Fr. (0)/Penn. (32), 10/30/81 - DEF. #2, 1981; 1 item (Item 172)
  - Princeton Fr./ Penn., 10/30/81 - Kicks, 1981; 1 item (Item 173)
  - Princeton Fr./ Penn., 10/28/83 - DEF #1, 1983; 1 item (Item 174)
  - Princeton Fr. (14)/Penn. (15), 10/30/81 - OFF. #2, 1981; 1 item (Item 175)
  - Princeton Fr. (0)/Penn. (32), 10/30/81 - DEF. #1, 1981; 1 item (Item 176)
  - Princeton vs. Penn. (FROSH), 11/1/80 - DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 177)
  - Princeton (14)/Penn. (15) Fr., 10/30/82 - OFF. #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 178)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/28/83 - Kicks, 1983; 1 item (Item 179)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 11/3/79 - OFF. #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 180)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/30/82 - OFF. #3, 1982; 1 item (Item 181)
  - Princeton (14)/Penn. (15) Fr., 10/30/82 - DEF. #2, 1982; 1 item (Item 182)
  - Princeton (14)/Penn. (15) Fr., 10/30/82 - DEF. #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 183)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/28/83 - OFF. #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 184)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/28/83 - OFF. #2, 1983; 1 item (Item 185)
  - Princeton/Cornell (FROSH), 10/18/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 186)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth (FROSH), 10/5/80 - Kicks, 1980; 1 item (Item 187)
  - Princeton, 9/12/80 - Kicks, 1980; 1 item (Item 188)
  - Princeton, 9/12/80 - Reel #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 189)
  - Princeton/Harvard (FROSH), 10/25/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 190)
  - Princeton/East Stroudsborg, 10/8/84 - Kicks, 1984; 1 item (Item 191)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth (FROSH), 10/5/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 192)
  - Princeton vs. Penn. (FROSH), 11/1/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 193)
  - Princeton vs. Penn. (FROSH), 11/1/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 194)
  - Princeton/Montclair, 10/6/80 - DEF., 1980; 1 item (Item 195)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth (FROSH), 10/5/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 196)
  - Princeton/Navy, 10/21/78 - Reel #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 197)
  - Princeton/Army (FROSH), 11/18/78 - OFF. #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 198)
  - Princeton/Army (FROSH), 11/18/78 - DEF. #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 199)
  - Princeton vs. Wilkes Scrimmage, 9/9/78 - Reel #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 200)
  - Princeton vs. Wilkes Scrimmage, 9/9/78 - Reel #3, 1978; 1 item (Item 201)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 10/10/78 - Reel #3, 1978; 1 item (Item 202)
  - Princeton/Rutgers, 9/30/78 - DEF. #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 203)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth - Reel #4, 1978; 1 item (Item 204)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 11/3/79 - DEF. #1, 1979; 1 item (Item 205)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 10/13/79 - OFF. #1, 1979; 1 item (Item 206)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 11/13/79 - DEF. #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 207)
  - Princeton Fr./Penn. Fr., 11/13/79 - Kicks, 1979; 1 item (Item 208)
  - Princeton/Columbia (FROSH), 10/10/80 - Kicks, 1980; 1 item (Item 209)
  - Princeton/Yale (FROSH), 11/15/80 - OFF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 210)
  - Princeton/Columbia (FROSH), 10/10/80 - OFF.#2, 1980; 1 item (Item 211)
  - Princeton/Yale (FROSH), 11/15/80 - Kicks, 1980; 1 item (Item 212)
  - Princeton/Yale (FROSH), 11/15/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 213)
  - Princeton/Yale (FROSH), 11/15/80 - DEF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 214)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 11/1/58 - Reel #3, 1958; 1 item (Item 215)
  - Princeton B. vs. Rutgers, 11/79 - Kicks, 1979; 1 item (Item 216)
  - Navy vs. Princeton University Freshmen, 10/19/73 - Reel: #1 DEF., 1 item (Item 217)
  - Columbia Freshmen vs. Princeton University, Reel #2 DEF., undated; 1 item (Item 218)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/11/1971 - 3rd Quarter, 1 item (Item 219)
  - Princeton vs. Rhode Island, 9/11/1971 - 4th Quarter, 1 item (Item 220)
  - Princeton/Penn., 10/25/74 - 3rd Quarter, 1974; 1 item (Item 221)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/22/71 - 3rd Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 222)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/22/71 - 2nd Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 223)
  - Princeton Fr. vs. Penn. Fr., 10/22/71 - 1st Quarter, 1971; 1 item (Item 224)
  - Princeton/Harvard (FROSH), 11/11/73 - DEF., 1973; 1 item (Item 225)
  - Princeton/Brooklyn College, 9/13/78 - Reel #1 OFF., 1978; 1 item (Item 226)
  - Princeton vs. Wilkes Scrimmage, 9/9/78 - Reel #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 227)
  - Princeton/Brooklyn College, 9/13/78 - Kicks, 1978; 1 item (Item 228)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 10/10/78 - Reel #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 229)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth - Reel #1, 1978; 1 item (Item 230)
  - Princeton/Cornell, 9/22/78 - OFF. #2, 1978; 1 item (Item 231)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/87, 1987; 1 item (Item 232)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/87 - OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 233)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/87 - OFF.#2, 1987; 1 item (Item 234)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/16/87 - Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 235)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/16/87 - DEF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 236)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/30/87 - DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 237)
  - Princeton (21)/Hofstra (0), 10/6/86 - Reel #5 Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 238)
  - Princeton (21)/Hofstra (0), 10/6/86 - Reel #5 OFF., 1986; 1 item (Item 239)
  - Princeton/Yale (FROSH) - 4th Quarter, 1988; 1 item (Item 240)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/87 - DEF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 241)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn. - DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 242)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/88 - DEF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 243)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/22/88 - Reels #5, DEF., 1988; 1 item (Item 244)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/87 - DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 245)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/16/87 - OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 246)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/16/87 - OFF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 247)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/28/88 - Reel #5 'Kicks', 1988; 1 item (Item 248)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/28/88 - Reel #5 DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 249)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/28/88 - Reel #5 DEF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 250)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/30/87 - OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 251)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/14/88 - Reel #5 DEF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 252)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn. - Kicks, 1988; 1 item (Item 253)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn. - Reels #5, DEF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 254)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/14/88 - Reel #5, 'Kicks', 1988; 1 item (Item 255)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/14/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 256)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/8/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 257)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/8/88 - Reel #5, 'Kicks', 1988; 1 item (Item 258)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/8/88 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 259)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/14/88 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 260)
  - Princeton (21)/Hofstra (0), 10/6/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 261)
  - Princeton (21)/Hofstra (0), 10/6/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 262)
  - Princeton (21)/Hofstra (0), 10/6/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 263)
  - Princeton/G.L. State, 10/20/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 264)
  - Columbia Freshman vs. Princeton University, #178 - Offense 1, undated; 1 item (Item 265)
  - Princeton/Yale (Frosh) - 4th Quarter, undated; 1 item (Item 266)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/3/90 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1990; 1 item (Item 267)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/9/90 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1 item (Item 268)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/20/90 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1990; 1 item (Item 269)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/26/90 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1990; 1 item (Item 270)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/90 - Reel #1, 1990; 1 item (Item 271)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/90 - Reel #2, 1990; 1 item (Item 272)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/90 - Reel #3, 1990; 1 item (Item 273)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/24/87 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 274)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/24/87 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 275)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/16/87 - DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 276)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/22/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 277)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/24/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #1 (Dupe from Harvard), 1987; 1 item (Item 278)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/30/87 - Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 279)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/27/84 - OFF. #1, 1984; 1 item (Item 280)
  - Princeton/Cornell (FROSH), 10/18/80 - OFF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 281)
  - Princeton/Cornell (FROSH), 10/18/80 - Kicks, 1980; 1 item (Item 282)
  - Princeton/Cornell (FROSH), 10/18/80 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 283)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth (FROSH), 10/5/80 - DEF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 284)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth (FROSH), 10/5/80 - OFF. #2, 1980; 1 item (Item 285)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/19/84 - OFF. #1, 1980; 1 item (Item 286)
  - Princeton/G.L. State, 10/20/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 287)
  - Princeton/G.L. State, 10/20/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 288)
  - Princeton/G.L. State, 10/20/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 289)
  - Maine - Bowdoin #2, 11/7/1964, 1 item (Item 290)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/4/87 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 291)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/4/87 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 292)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/4/87 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 293)
  - Princeton/G.L. Boro, 10/20/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 294)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/4/87 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 295)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/14/89 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 296)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/3/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 297)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/3/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 298)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/12/90 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1990; 1 item (Item 299)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/20/89 - Reel #6, DEF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 300)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/20/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 301)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/3/89 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1989; 1 item (Item 302)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/14/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 303)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/8/89 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 304)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/8/89 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 305)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/14/88 - Reels #5, OFF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 306)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/12/88 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1988; 1 item (Item 307)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/12/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1988; 1 item (Item 308)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/12/88 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 309)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/8/88 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 310)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/22/88 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1988; 1 item (Item 311)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/1/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 312)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/1/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 313)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 11/1/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 314)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/15/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 315)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/15/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 316)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/4/87 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 317)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/11/89 - Reel #5, DEF. 2, 1989; 1 item (Item 318)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/14/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 319)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/14/89 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1989; 1 item (Item 320)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/8/89 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1989; 1 item (Item 321)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/8/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 322)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/11/89 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 323)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/11/89 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1989; 1 item (Item 324)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/11/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 325)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/8/89 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1989; 1 item (Item 326)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/11/89 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1989; 1 item (Item 327)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/24/87 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 328)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/24/87 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 329)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/30/87 - DEF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 330)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Penn., 10/30/87 - OFF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 331)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Springfield, 9/13/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 332)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Springfield, 9/13/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 333)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/14/87 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 334)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/14/87 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 335)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/14/87 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1987; 1 item (Item 336)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/5/86 - Reel #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 337)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/15/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 338)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 339)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 340)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 341)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 342)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/17/86 - Reel #5, OFF #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 343)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/5/86 - Reel #3, 1986; 1 item (Item 344)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/5/86 - Reel #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 345)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 346)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/17/86 - Reel #5, OFF #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 347)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 348)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Harvard, 10/25/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 349)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/17/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 350)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/17/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 351)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Cornell, 10/17/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 352)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/86 - Reel #5, Kicks, 1986; 1 item (Item 353)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Columbia, 10/10/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 354)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Springfield, 9/13/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #2, 1986; 1 item (Item 355)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Springfield, 9/13/86 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 356)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/14/87 - Reel #5, OFF. #1, 1987; 1 item (Item 357)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Yale, 11/14/87 - Reel #5, DEF. #2, 1987; 1 item (Item 358)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Springfield, 9/13/86 - Reel #5, DEF. #1, 1986; 1 item (Item 359)
  - FROSH - Princeton/Dartmouth - OFF. #1, undated; 1 item (Item 360)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 10/8/79 - DEF #2, 1979; 1 item (Item 361)
  - Princeton/Upsala, 10/8/79 - Kicks, 1979; 1 item (Item 362)
  - Princeton Merchant Marine, 9/4/82 - Kicks, 1982; 1 item (Item 363)
  - Princeton/Harvard, 10/20/88 - Reel #5 OFF. #2, 1988; 1 item (Item 364)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/79 - Kicks, 1979; 1 item (Item 365)
  - Princeton/Dartmouth, 10/7/79 - OFF. #1, 1979; 1 item (Item 366)
  - Princeton/Wilkes, 9/10/82 - DEF. #1, 1982; 1 item (Item 367)